# JONATHAN ENRIQUEZ

Full-stack | App Developer

## FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT

HTML5 CSS3 Javascript jQuery Material

#### LANGUAGES

Javascript Swift Python

#### **DATABASES**

MongoDB SQLite Firebase MvSOL

#### **SERVERS**

Node.js Django Flask

#### **FRAMEWORKS**

Angular 5 Express Socket.io Twitter Bootstrap Google Materialize

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Recently graduated Web and App Developer proficient in the iOS, MEAN, and Python stacks, specializing in iOS and Back-End technologies. Strong attention to detail, with the ability to swiftly adapt to new challenges. Diligent worker, often putting in more work hours than the most. Excellent communicator and a team player, known for taking leadership roles in groups.

## **EDUCATION**

CODING DOJO | BURBANK, CA | 2017-2018

#### Black Belt Web Development

- Spent approximately 768+ hours of intensive study across two frameworks (Python and MEAN stacks) earning a Black Belt, the highest measure of achievement (earning perfect scores on the exams).
- As part of a four-member-team, completed and presented a project in Python (utilizing SQLite and Django) of a sample E-Commerce site.)

#### Black Belt Web Development

- Spent over 260 hours of intensive study to learn how to produce applications with Xcode, while earning a Black Belt, the highest measure of achievement (earning a perfect score on the exam).
- As part of a three-member team, competed and won first prize in two 24-hour iOS
  hackathons held at the Dojo. The first project utilized Core Motion to create a simple
  Galaga-style game which doesn't utilize any buttons for gameplay. The second was a
  project which utilized iOS's Core Location to create an interval runner training
  application, which has been further developed in the following weeks.

CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY | LOS ANGELES, CA | 2002-2007 Bachelor of Arts, Psychology.

## WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

#### Coders. On Demand | Python

Built a tongue-in-cheek E- $\check{\text{C}}$ ommerce site connecting Coding Dojo students concerned about their ability to pass their belt exams with experienced coders willing to take the exams on their behalf.

 $Technologies: Python, \, Django, \, SQLite, \, Twitter \,\, Bootstrap, \, HTML5, \, CSS3, \, Humor. \,\, The contraction of the contrac$ 

## Unnamed E-Commerce Project | Python

Current project creating an E-Commerce site that would allow individual consumers to pool their resources for purchasing from retailers at bulk prices. Technologies: Socket.io, Python, Django, MySQL, Twitter Bootstrap, HTML5, & CSS3.

## Personal Website | MEAN

Completed a personal site detailing my coding journey and expounding on my skillset. Technologies: JavaScript, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express.js, Angular, Angular Material, Materialize, Node.js, HTML5, and CSS3.

## **APP DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS**

#### Runner's HIIE | iOS

Continuing with what began during the second iOS Coding Dojo hackathon, this project allows gives runners an ability to set a baseline personal high intensity speed.

Technologies: Firebase, Swift, Core Location, Charts, Hero.

#### Anonymous Dojo I iOS

Built an anonymous chat app using Apple's Multipeer Connectivity

Technologies: Swift, Multipeer Connectivity, Core Data, iQKeyboard.

#### Who Da Fastest? | iOS

In the early stages of development, a Watch-OS party game for people to see who can achieve the highest speed.

Technologies: Swift, Hero, Core Data.

#### **COURSES IN PROGRESS**

UDEMY | Angular with Angular Material, Angularfire... | Schwarzmuller UDEMY | Electron for Desktop Apps... | Grider

## OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

CASE MANAGER Special Service for Groups | Los Angeles, CA| 2014-2017 EDUCATOR FOR SPECIAL-NEEDS ADULTS | MERCI | Monterey Park, CA| 2013-2014

#### CONTACT

P: +626 252 5678

W: www.jonathanenriquez.tech

E: jonathanmerniquez@yahoo.com

L: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ jonathan-enriquez/

G: https://github.com/ JonathanMEnriquez